

1800 102 2558 | +91 9818882211







Software professional with 10+ years of experience Seeking lead/managerial roles in Application Support, Production Support, Release Management, JIRA, Unix Shell Scripting, SQL Server, ServiceNow, Autosys



Total Experience: 10 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Notice Period: 1 Month

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electronics/Telecommunication]

Current Designation: Process Manager

Current Company: Ederx
Current Location: Pune
Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Pune, Delhi / NCR

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Team Lead/Tech Lead

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services
Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Team Lead/Tech Lead,Application Support,Release Management,Incident Management,Problem Management,Change Management,ITIL,JIRA,Unix Shell scripting,SQL Server,Servicenow,Production Support,Application Management,SQL,AutoSys,PLSQL

Verified : Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 23-Jan-21 Last Modified: 23-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

 $A Competent Software \ Professional \ with \ 10+ years \ of \ experience \ in \ Application \ Support \ Management (L2/L3 \ Support)$

Extensive Hands on Experience with Oracle, PL/SQL, Unix Shell Scripts, Autosys, Service Now, Jira, ITIL

Basic knowledge of Investment banking

Astrong team player with excellent communication, interpersonal, analytical and management skills

Work Experience

Eclerx as Process Manager Jul 2018 to Till Date

Process feeds from various vendors using Asset Control.

Preparation of Release Plan, coordinate with various teams for the release and Deploy Code into Production and UAT Configure and run Tidal batches in UAT and Production

Monitor batches, services and server status from Geneos

Make shell scripts to automate daily task

Making of Confluences and Wiki pages

J P Morgan Chase & Co as Associate

Jul 2017 to Feb 2018

- * Regulatory Reporting in various countries.
- * Maintain UAT and Production environment.
- Upgrades (Releases) in UAT and Prod environments
- * Debug Unix and PL/SQL codes like Shell scripts and Procedure/Functions etc.

HCL Tech as Senior Software Engineer

Aug 2012 to Jul 2017

Project Credit Risk Management Client Nomura Period Aug 2012- Present

Tools DB Artisan, Putty Connection Manager, RapidSQL

Job Scheduler Autosys

Operating System Windows XP, Unix Scripting Unix Shell Scripts

Role Production Support Executive
Responsibilities * Calculation of Exposures for Counterparties by running batches on Unix and Windows.

* Skills to Investigate and find the blocking points where Application engine fails, to valuate & implement solutions

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld. accordingly and providing L2 support to issues raised by Front and Middle office users with respect to data quality.

- Diagnosis, Resolving and management of major production outages and coordinating with different teams across the globe for resolution of issues.
- Handling user queries
- Deploy the code in production (Releases)
- Automate daily tasks by writing shell scripts

TCS as Production Support Executive

Mar 2010 to Aug 2012

Project RDT Support

Client JP Morgan Chase Period November 2010- Present

ETL Informatica

Tools SQL Server management Studio Express 9, DBSQL, Putty Manager, SQL Developer

Job Scheduler Control – M Operating System Windows XP, Unix Role Production Support Executive

Responsibilities Dealing with user queries.
Root Cause Analysis of the failure of the jobs and errors in the applications.
To deploy the code in Production (Releases)

To generate reports on Oracle for the specific applications. To perform some Start of the day and End of the Day checks.

Status reporting.

To run the jobs/feeds in Unix.

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Kurukshetra University in 2009

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

ITIL Foundation V3

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Unix shell scripting		2020	9 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
PL/SQL		2020	5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
RapidSQL, Putty Connection Manager		2020	7 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Oracle	11 G	2020	9 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
AUTOSYS	R11	2018	2 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
AUTOSYS	4.5	2017	4 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
ITIL Foundation	V3	2017	
SQL DEVELOPER		2020	
TOAD		2017	
Service now		2020	5 Year(s) 3 Month(s)

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Punjabi				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Job Type: Permanent Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved @ 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.